[crying]
Stopping aside.
Good morning guys.  I am standing outside the house and going to
buy bananas.  Brother,
give me six bananas.  Ignore the situation right now.  Hi
welcome back to my blog guys.  I am
in a bad condition.  My hair gets very frizzy.
I am so exhausted and red
because I pushed my limits today.
I love to
push my limits in my workouts.
But I also feel scared.  There is a
great fear of muscle injury.  If you have gained heavy weight
and your
demand is very high,
brother, it is like this,
I thought it was something from outside, a
guest, okay,
look, your father can never say anything good, sometimes he can't
say anything good,
last vlogging, I
mean, if you practice for three more months, I will go otherwise,
oh brother, I was crying, I swear, I was crying, do
n't
ask your mother to go out, I was
crying standing here,
happy birthday to you, Kamakshi dash mare, oh one,
Kamakshi dash mare, yes, that's what she said, saying
love,
yes, roast roast, hello guys,
so guys, I'm not, so guys, friend, this is enough for
me, guys 21 doona 22, I just
saw in a recent vlog,
Kamakshi is looking so hot, guys, Kamakshi has
switched on her personality, guys,
when someone like this comes into your life, you change, it's not like that
and change is good, good, what I feel,
you don't love, people will say I'm very
handsome, no, Anjali, Zara's looking very good
Kamaksha is wearing a T-shirt, you will
ask for a penis and it is bad bad, it
looks very cute, friend, I also want this stomach, I am
not able to get it, I am not able to get it, so I have come
again, I have to do all the shopping
and then we will have lunch
and this is the first time you have come alone with me, I have
come alone before also out of compulsion [laughs] you are so
cunning, so
cunning.  We come a lot but
mostly with Mayank.  We have
come to S today.   Didn't
even ask.
Yes, I did not ask today.  We came alone today.  Guys, while walking
we saw our followers.  He's going back
in the suit.  Oh she came she came she came.
Sir marriage
marriage Kamakshi.  I don't know
where we were by that.  Suddenly I forgot.  Today is
Kamakshi's birthday.
Today I will go to nka lux.  I have a big heart.   I will
definitely go shopping today.
I will also buy makeup today.  And Zara, we are already leaving.
Zara is here by the way.  Today is this girl's
birthday and she is celebrating her last birthday with us.  She is
celebrating her last birthday with us, that is, her last birthday before marriage.   Are you
giving?   It
is at home for you.
I have yes you like it.  You wanted that
stuff to go in your dowry.
Yes.
No lipstick.
Where do you want to go for your work?
Mercedes.
Sell ​​it.  sell me.  Where has Mercedes gone
?
So it doesn't look like those two girls who are
roaming around like a loafers, camera utha ke
chapri si bahar aayi, I will be the
last person who will do it to anyone,
I be yourself
man [laughs]
chal coach chalega, guys if it is not in DLF then
we will have to go to City Walk for Zara,
Anayka is not in City Walk so we have to
come back here because our booking is here.
Guys so we did shopping from nkaa.  We
shopped at Zara.  I
bought the new lipstick from nka.  Now Kamakshi and I have come to
Daily Hus for lunch.
I got this.  I haven't gotten into PR yet.
So I thought why not.  I
was very confused because I know that
mostly I come in the PR of NK and
will come in new launches.  This is shade
Velvety.  I bought this because I was
confused as to which one I should buy.  Soft
velvet and another nude shade.  Very beautiful.
Its formula is exactly the same as
Pyare Pari's lipstick.  I mean, pretty much
90% of the time, I love that lipstick.
So now Aunty and I will eat something
and then we will go back and then
this girl will throw a party again in the evening.  This girl will
throw her birthday party again.  how often?
So let's see, I will eat something healthy.
This is very cute.  I will
also tag it here for you.  I will tag this.  There
is no natural light right now.  Give me yours.
I will show you the light.  It looks
so beautiful with the brown lip liner the shade
is so good.  nka
it is so pretty.  Look at this lipstick,
Alia, leave it.
So Happy is
this.  I am buying the stuff.  No
guys I have a gift for you.  So guys,
Kamakshi always likes white sauce pasta,
in her five years of marriage in Bali, she
tried this, all oio, and after that,
she loves pasta and alfo,
yes this is one, and I tried it at home too, it is
quite spicy, actually the
taste of olive oil is a little less in it, but it is
spicy, I added Tabasco in this because I
love more chilli, I have also ordered some
chilli, so this is her date, we have to
enjoy our date, guys, we have come home.  Oh, it's
very cute.  I said
just for you this is written so
happy birthday.  Now Kamakshi will say that she will take
care of it for the whole year.  I will take her back to her in-laws' house.
What happened?   Okay guys.
Kamakshi came home and Kamakshi got
such a cute surprise from her elder
sister in law.  Big
elder sister in law entire family.
Okay, from the family or from everyone from the
in-laws' side, oh it's nice,
my choice is Purva,
no choice Purva, yours, oh pretty, oh pretty,
I remember my time in Hyderabad, jewellery,
I used to love you like this, the
cake has also come, we will cut it in the
evening from the family, oh Purva, thank
you for the gift, Kamakshi liked it very much,
oh friend [laughs]
come on, bye bye, are
you playing this clean-cut dress, hey, what are
you going to do, do
n't be a jerk, look, I am your
aunt, I am
giving you this look, look at your son's look, you got your
hair done,
what are you going to do, friend,
look, what are you going to do, oh what are you going to do, you are
not going,
you are like this, then the cake will be cut now, Kamakshi's
mom, it's not your birthday, when you should
roam around so much, mom, don't roam around.
Mother and daughter have just had a cold war.
Hello mother.
Hello son.   Yes friend.
Happy
to you.  Happy
to you.
Brother,
take this completely.  Whom should I feed you, friend?  What should I bring?   Do
n't know when?
Happy Birthday.
No, my clothes will get dirty.
Birthday clothes are clothes, please bring them
for aunt.  I have brought this gift for my aunt.
She will take it herself in a while.  That's why I
brought it.
So we have come to our venue for dinner,
guys, burn out, this is our second car, let's
go, this is the first burn out, what is this
here,
hey, don't start hitting, guys,
we have sent mom and dad home,
mom, dad and the kids have gone home, now we are going to do
Gokati, we will edit 10 minutes 8 times at night, it is
very bad,
mine is so bad, but I was thinking something else
brother.  So we're going to do 10:00 p.m.
Godard, the last film we did was
in Bangkok, Thailand.   That's
good.  We did it on a hot afternoon.  Now
when are we going at night?  Kamakshi we
street day guys.
You guys on that side, its
The Next Day.
Good afternoon guys.  So yesterday evening went quite well.
Yesterday was a great day.  But today
I am down.  I can make a video of you too.
So I went down.  I'm feeling low today.
I just had my lunch.  I had cooked rice.
Myesha this is bad.  This is very bad.  Myesha had
eaten these herself.  I don't
like it very much.  It's too young.  Myesha also
likes it very much.  So I told Mysha that you have
spilled it in the room, so you will clean it yourself.
So instead of cleaning, it is doing something else.
I don't know what to do.   Elder brother.
Okay, just say bye.  Well,
like you said yesterday.  Guys, if you liked it, please
like, subscribe [laughs]
and follow me here.
Guys if you like this video then like and
subscribe.  Guys if you like this video then
follow and comment and
like and subscribe.  Bye.
Oh, now you say it too.  If you also feel like it.
No, just
say it.
No.
Say.  You wanted to speak.  I heard.
Our Mahima wanted to speak.  Say.
No.
Sure.
Yes.
Myshu, she is not saying that.  Then you tell me.
I am also not saying anything until Mahima
says that I will do something else like magic, bye bye guys, see
you in the next blog or you guys
want me to do a vlog, I am not able to do it, right now
I will not do it for two-three days anyway,
but the video of I will do what I eat in a day, I will do, I will do because
you
people like it and it will also help you,
children do this only after coming from school.
Let's see you in the next video bye.
[music]
yes